前頭路途險峻又長遠
There's a long and winding road ahead
幾朵烏雲遮住臉
A few black clouds lay over head
而那太陽卻總是不見蹤影
And the shining sun is nowhere to be seen
但你只要起身繼續走
But with every step and fall you take
敢於接受新事物
all your thoughts and leaps of faith
雨過似乎就一定會有天青
There's a silver lining somewhere in between
閉上眼
Close your eyes
深呼吸
Breathe in slow
緩緩吐氣
Then let it go
當旅途漸漸變長
Stop and smell the roses
停下來聞聞玫瑰花香
when your journey's getting long
當生命想唱反調
When you feel your life's against you
而讓你全身毫無能量
and your energy is gone
並非誰都知道何時
'Cause not everybody knows when
該讓自己放個鬆
it's just time to catch a break
當你累到只想自己靜一靜時
When you're draining
and you just don't wanna show it
停下來聞聞玫瑰花香
Stop and smell the roses
今天又有了新點子
Today has found another way
想將昨天帶回到眼前
to turn right into yesterday
只因時間又再次熄滅了光源
'Cause time has taken all the light again
就算我擺弄著現實
But if I fiddle with reality
想試圖改變我的未來
to try and change who I should be
最後還不是仍然呆站在起點
I'm tucking my own destiny in bed
閉上眼
Close your eyes
深呼吸
Breathe in slow
緩緩吐氣
Then let it go
當旅途漸漸變長
Stop and smell the roses
停下來聞聞玫瑰花香
when your journey's getting long
當生命想唱反調
When you feel your life's against you
而讓你全身毫無能量
and your energy is gone
並非誰都知道何時
'Cause not everybody knows when
該讓自己放個鬆
it's just time to catch a break
當你累到只想自己靜一靜時
When you're draining
and you just don't wanna show it
當旅途漸漸變長
Stop and smell the roses
停下來聞聞玫瑰花香
when your journey's getting long
當生命想唱反調
When you feel your life's against you
而讓你全身毫無能量
and your energy is gone
並非誰都知道何時
'Cause not everybody knows when
該讓自己放個鬆
it's just time to catch a break
當你累到只想自己靜一靜時
When you're draining
and you just don't wanna show it
停下來聞聞玫瑰花香
Stop and smell the roses